[Music]
what I got now it's like I scored a
touchdown I'm feeling shorty cuz I only
feel a touch now I quit the range and
playing the games and even tossed out my
little black book for the names because
I got a lady that don't trip when I roll
out only if you know what I mean feel me
no doubt so word is b and yeah I B still
tight I ain't got to spend a dollar just
to make it feel right yeah slow motion
for me stick like a posted on me do the
spin like a skew slow roast it for me
this ain't a talk show but you the view
baby girl stay fly like a beauty do why
your boy get back to his Dy boo another
day another dollar I'mma holler at you
but before I bounce one last request
move like a snake for me baby no contest
within a couple seconds you could always
tell if you got a match or you never
will is it fake or is it real do you
want to grab her or just grab the bill
cuz only you could tell when love is
dead and you could always tell when
nothing's dead is it a lifetime is it
the one night is it all good or is it
not right I got to go I can't stay I got
to roll I can't play I got to hit the
studio record a tight track then do the
show to make the though and I'll be
right back I got to go I can't stay I
got to roll I can't play I got to hit
the studio record a tight track then do
the show to make the door and I'll be
right back love is it a gift or a curse
is it For Better or For Worse is it the
b or a Hearst yo you got to ask yourself
first love is it a gift or a curse
is it For Better or For Worse is it the
b or a hearse yo you got to ask yourself
first yo I love the way you move I love
the way you talk I love your attitude I
won't forget the way you walk I'm
feeling you hey you knew this girl you
know you feeling me now let's do this
girl I love the way you move I love the
way you talk I love your attitude I
won't forget the way you walk I'm
feeling you and you knew this girl you
know you feeling me